http://www.laserstar.net/en/info/privacy/

English
Español (Spanish)
LaserStarTV
Laser WeldingIndustrial Laser WeldingJewelry Laser WeldingLaser EngravingIndustrial Laser Marking & EngravingJewelry Laser Marking & EngravingDeep Engraving VideosTactical Weapon CustomizationLaser CuttingIndustrial CuttingJewelry CuttingProduct PresentationsLaser Welding Systems - PresentationLaser Marking Systems - PresentationInjection Mold Repair Mold Repair VideosMiscellaneous VideosCustomer Testimonials
LaserStar Academy
LaserStar Technologies Corporation Privacy Statement
Effective January 1, 2011The mission of LaserStar Technologies Corporation (the “Company”) and the LaserStar Technologies Corporation web site (the “Site”) is to provide all Users (as defined below) with general information about the Company and to allow Registered Users (as defined below) to receive certain additional information from the Company, and to submit certain information to the Company, including specific product or purchasing information, in a secure exchange.  The Company is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that you understand how information about you or your company may be collected and used.  The Company’s web platform offers a secure exchange of information between the Company and you.  This Privacy Policy sets forth the policies and procedures that the Company undertakes to protect your information and the terms and conditions upon which the Company provides information to you.  This Privacy Policy will explain in more detail the following topics: •          Information collection•           Usage of information by the Company•           Usage of information by third parties•           Usage of information provided by the Company to you•           Information storage and security•           Links to other web sites•           How to access and change personally identifiable information•           Change of ownership•           How to contact the Company•           Privacy policy changesInformation CollectionYou can browse certain portions of the Site without registering as a user (“Non-Registered User”). If you choose to provide the Company with registration information (“Registered User,” and together with Non-Registered Users, “Users”), the Company collects the information that you submit to provide services to you, improve the functionality offered to you and other Users and understand how Users become interested in utilizing the Site.  The Company collects this information directly from Registered Users through the registration and information submission process and from all Users by automated scripts via cookies or standard web logs. Your registration/account information:  If you wish to become a Registered User, the Company requires you to provide your name, your job title, your company name, your company address, your company email address and telephone number in order for the Company to provide you with certain services.  The Company also requires you to select a private password in order to access the secure portions of the Site.  The Company does not require, nor solicit, personal information about you such as home address or telephone number. The Company may require financial and billing information in connection with certain submissions or purchases made by you through the Site.  The Company does not use this financial or billing information for marketing or promotional purposes. Except as the Company explicitly states at the time it requests information, or as provided for in the LaserStar Technologies Corporation Terms of Use, the Company does not disclose the information you provide to third parties.How information is collected:  In addition to you uploading or submitting information to the Site, the Company may use cookies and standard web log files to automatically collect information about you in order to operate and improve the Site.A “cookie” is a small file on your computer that the Company uses to recognize you when you return to the Site.  You may not be able to interact with the Site if your browser does not accept cookies from the Company.  The Company also uses standard web logs to collect information, including your IP address, operating system, web browser, ISP and referring/exit web pages. The Company will not share with third parties any personally identifiable information collected from such cookies or web logs but may share with its business partners anonymous information collected from cookies or web logs, as well as demographic information that is not personally identifiable.Usage of Information by the CompanyThe Company uses the information collected on the Site to perform, improve and offer additional services to Users of the Site. Information that is not personally identifiable may be collected on all Users and is used to understand how Non-Registered Users choose to become Registered Users.  The Company may disclose your personal information when required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: comply with legal process; enforce the LaserStar Technologies Corporation Terms of Use; respond to claims that such information violates the rights of third-parties; respond to claims that personal information (e.g. phone number, street address) of a third-party has been transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, other users or the general public.  The Company will notify you of such disclosure when reasonable and permitted by law.Usage of Information by Third PartiesThe Company does not sell, rent or share your personally identifiable information with third parties for purposes other than providing services to you, except where required to by law. No personally identifiable information on Non-Registered Users of the Site is shared with third parties.Usage of Information Provided by the Company to YouThe Company may provide Registered Users with certain product specific information through the Site.  If you are the recipient of such information, you agree to consider the information confidential and shall take reasonable actions to protect and maintain the confidentiality of such information, and shall protect the disclosure of such information in any form whatsoever, pursuant to the terms of the LaserStar Technologies Corporation Terms of Use; provided that you may share such information with your agents, employees, attorneys, accountants, or other representatives (collectively, “Authorized Representatives”) on a need-to-know basis only. You agree to be responsible for any disclosures of the Company’s confidential information by you or your Authorized Representatives. Information Storage and SecurityThe Company takes the security of your information very seriously.  The Company uses commercially reasonable efforts to maintain industry standards and best practices to store your information in a secure environment.  The Company stores your data in a tier-one secured access data center and regularly perform audits of our system for possible vulnerabilities.  The Company uses Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) for all communication between your browser and the Site.  Access to your information on the Company’s servers from browsers is protected by an encrypted password. Your account profile is password-protected so that only you have access to your account information. In order to maintain this protection, do not give your password to anyone. If anyone ever asks you for information claiming they are LaserStar Technologies Corporation staff, contact the Company at privacy@laserstar.net.  If you share a computer, you should sign out of your account and close the browser window before someone else logs on. Links to Other Web SitesYou may occasionally see or be directed to links to other web sites on the Site.  The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites you may visit through a link you found on the Site.  If you provide information directly to a party other than the Company, different privacy policies may cover those parties’ use of your information.  Please review any company’s privacy policy before disclosing your personal or company information.Access and Change Personally Identifiable InformationYou may access and change your information collected by the Company at any time.  This information includes your basic account information and any additional information that you provided.  The Company removes information you provide to it from its servers upon termination of your Registered User account.  However, if you have requested the Company to save your account or login information indefinitely and provided the Company with an alternative email, then the Company will save your account and login information in case you decide to become a Registered User again at a later date.Change of OwnershipIn the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of the Company’s Registered User account information, including email and postal addresses, to a separate entity. All Registered Users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of the Company’s assets by a third party, and may choose to modify any of their account information at that time.Contact the CompanyIf you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email the Company at privacy@laserstar.net or contact the Company at:LaserStar Technologies CorporationAttn: Privacy PolicyOne Industrial CourtRiverside, RI 02915Telephone:  (401) 438-1500Email:  privacy@laserstar.netRevisions to This Privacy PolicyThe Company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy and its other policies and agreements at any time. Notice of any revisions, amendments, or modifications will be posted on the Site, and a User’s continued use of the Site will signify agreement to such changes.Recent Updates:  On January  21, 2011, this Privacy Policy was posted to the Site.
Info
Request Pricing Info
Contact Us
Download Our Catalog
×
Developer Tools
Database Activity
Performance Tracking
